glory to Ukraine to the heroes glory I think that the
слава украине героям слава я думаю что
whole world will help you you will open you
вам поможет весь мир вы откроетесь вас
will you will prosper and we will be in
будет вы будете процветать а мы будем в
such an ass in the coming years good afternoon
такой жопе ближайшие годы добрый день
good afternoon glory to Ukraine to the heroes glory
добрый день слава украине героям слава
you are where the flowers are from
вы откуда цветки
but I don’t have Ukraine where
но я нет украины откуда
from grow bonus usually children swear from Russia
из расти бонус обычно с россии ругаются
or there it immediately arched out, isn’t it, I
дети или там сразу выгнула нет ли не я
’m not one of the stupid heads,
не вхожу в число глупо головок
you don’t support the bouclé war,
вы не поддерживаете войну букле не
I don’t absolutely support it, I don’t
я не поддерживаю абсолютно я не просто
just say glory to Ukraine, I think that
так говорю слава украине я считаю что им
they really are the glory of Russia, it’s just a
вам действительно слава россии просто
shame and you have many long years of shame
позор и и долгие долгие годы позора у
some acquaintances who fought there,
вас есть какие-то знакомые которые там
for example, died a lot
воевали на примере погибли очень много
like yours,
как вот ваш
I’m afraid to call, that is, you are a doctor before
я боюсь призывать то есть вы медик до
us, doctors, too, in the entire post
нас медики тоже во всем постсоветском
-Soviet space, doctors were
пространстве медики были
liable for military service,
военнообязанными на
but you don’t seem to be doing mobilization,
но у вас же вроде не делают мобилизацию
well, you rumors are scary
ну вы слухи ходят страшно
because full-scale  a war without
потому как полномасштабная война без
love for a cause, in general, it would be
любви за дело это вообще было бы
people not, although they never sit, you know,
люди не хотя никогда сидят знаете
never, these men are a feature for
никогда вот эти мужики особенность для
grandfather, everything is taken  ha and here he is right for you
дедуся все берега и вот он правильно вас
there so that you are against on the tatami then all the
там чтобы вы против на татами тогда все
same but while he is sitting there
же но пока он там сидит
read here and restore
читались сюда и восстанавливать
justice about the darkness he does not want
справедливость про темноту он не хочет
I don’t think that if they have to announce
я не думаю что если должны объявить
mobilization that there will be many who want to
мобилизацию что будет много желающих
tell Khokhloma that you are here we will
рассказывает хохлому шо вы тут мы вас
tear you  like sitting there in siberia it's one
порвем типа сидя там в сибири это одно
greedy and then it's getting harder
падких а затем это все тяжелее
for me actually the whole world for the whole
у меня на самом деле весь мир на весь
world is amazed at your courage your
мир поражен вами вашим мужеством вашим
heroism of our people and you
геройством нашего народа и у вас все
will be fine it will all end sooner or
будет хорошо это все закончится рано или
later yes it's all horror it's terrible it is  it doesn’t
поздно да это все ужас это ужасно это не
fit in my head, but it will end,
укладывается в голове но это закончится
I think that the whole world will
я думаю что вам поможет весь мир вы от
help you, you will build up, you will prosper,
строитесь вас будет вы будете процветать
and we will be in such a group for the next few years
а мы будем в такой группе ближайшие годы
that I don’t think that in Russia they didn’t
что не думаю что в россии на иное не
expect such a resistance nude,
ожидали чтобы такое сопротивление nude
they thought that there in two-  they’ll take three days and
думали что там за два-три дня захватят и
that’s it, and already on the third day, in general, it
все да а уже на третий день в общем-то
was clear that my husband had all new facets,
было понятно что мужу все новые грани
well, we have, I’ll tell you, most of us,
ну у нас я вам скажу у нас большинство
probably 90 percent of the population, is
наверное 90 процентов населения
drowning the gate  you’re driving around the city
топит вороти у нас вот по городу едешь
right now on May 9th, these flags will soon be sold in
сейчас же 9 мая скоро продают эти флаги
letters, to declare in
буквами заявить
letters on cars, but it’s true, it’s just that
буквами на машинах но это правда просто
at one
в один момент
moment something happened that you realized that
как то произошло что то что ты понял что
you live among just some morons,
ты живешь среди просто каких-то дебилов
it’s very hard actually  I understand living in
это очень тяжело на самом деле жить вот
this situation, well, on the other
этой обстановке понимаю ну с другой
hand, I understand that
стороны я понимаю что россияне почему
why Russians hate Russians now, I absolutely agree with this and I’m
сейчас и россиян ненавидят я с этим
even ready to
абсолютно согласна и готова даже
suffer in this mass,
страдать в этой массе
I’m one Russian scary dude
меня вот один русский страшно чувак
right away, your Ukrainians start swearing at me there
сразу ваши украинцы на меня там начинают
and I’m already green if people have
ругаться и грину уже если у людей
they bombed houses so it didn’t go to the point not
разбомбили дома так не зашло точки не
again they are angry at you because you are a
снова они злые на тебя потому что ты
representative of this country and how would you
представитель этой страны и как бы и ты
support this war in Ukraine there, of
поддерживаешь там войну эту в украине то
course, how they should relate, but
конечно как они должны относиться а
it’s understandable in general, of course,
понятно вообще конечно
that is, if we came somewhere
то есть если если бы мы пришли где-то
there  they killed like his relatives he
там поубивали типа его родственников он
was so angry himself and you yourself about this
был так сама злой был и ты сам об этом
idiot idiot
придурке идиот это
you know the most interesting thing I noticed
самое знаете что интересное я заметил
the poorer people do so they are somewhere in
чем беднее люди так делать они где-то
Tomsk ho  i live in siberia
томске хоть деревнях живую там в сибири
there, so they want more like to show
так и тем они больше хотят типа показать
americano there,
американо то там
that is, I say that listen, I’m looking at
то есть я говорю что слушай я вот смотрю
people who run and want to live in
люди есть которые бегают хотят жить в
america, there is britain in europe, but on the
америке там британия в европе но
contrary, something is not coming to you in
наоборот что-то вот к тебе в сибирь эту
siberia  they run to your village,
не бегут в твою деревню
why is that johnson there then your
зачем там тому джонсону тогда твоя
village.  he can’t play out with his problems,
деревня . он со своими проблемами не
but there is, yes, on this, a
может разыграться но есть да вот на этом
person somehow compensates for his,
человек как-то компенсирует вот своем
let’s say, unrealized life, so he’s
скажем нереализованность жизни так вот
limited, he is realized by the fact that
ограничен он реализован тем что вот
somewhere there is a nuclear cudgel and
где-то там есть ядерная дубина и его из
his nation is respected there, for
это там уважают его нацию этому ради
whom he is  they are flawed, they
кого он они ущербные у них появился
finally have a meaning in life, at least some, they
наконец смысл в жизни хоть какое-то они
can feel like someone is a
могут почувствовать себя кем-то
person as
человеком как
there is a drunkard there, so that's all the lady is
есть там пьяница так вот все даму
blinking, but he went in there a debauch in the mouth
blinking а вот он зашел там дебош в уста
all the way from fled from the year I eat or
все сторону от бежали от год я ем или
how and then  put on sonic
как а затем наденьте sonic
youth the fountain pays off yea ok
youth фонтан окупается да хорошо всем
thank you all came by evenings and may you
спасибо зашел вечера и пусть у вас всё
be fine
будет хорошо